[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What went -- what went on out there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "went", "--", "what", "went", "on", "out", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, I think the fact that we're talking about it on Mitt Romney's big night tells you it was a distraction.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "fact", "that", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "it", "on", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "big", "night", "tells", "you", "it", "was", "a", "distraction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Did you find it embarrassing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "find", "it", "embarrassing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "How do you rate it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "rate", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "It's a very close race, and so you have to understand success is in the eye of the beholder.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "very", "close", "race", ",", "and", "so", "you", "have", "to", "understand", "success", "is", "in", "the", "eye", "of", "the", "beholder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN"], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Were you palpitating?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "palpitating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "No!", "answer_tokens": ["No", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood", "Clint Eastwood"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Were you thinking, What the hell is Dirty Harry doing up there?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "thinking", ",", "What", "the", "hell", "is", "Dirty", "Harry", "doing", "up", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Look, Clint Eastwood is Clint Eastwood, and the crowd loved it.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "Clint", "Eastwood", "is", "Clint", "Eastwood", ",", "and", "the", "crowd", "loved", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Who made the better speech, Mitt or Ann Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "made", "the", "better", "speech", ",", "Mitt", "or", "Ann", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Mitt.", "answer_tokens": ["Mitt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Has he resonated with America's women?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "resonated", "with", "America", "'s", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Yes, absolutely, the whole convention.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", ",", "the", "whole", "convention", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "You know Clint Eastwood well.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "Clint", "Eastwood", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What did you -- what did you make of what happened tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "--", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "happened", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, listen, I think it depends on which side you're on in all of this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "I", "think", "it", "depends", "on", "which", "side", "you", "'re", "on", "in", "all", "of", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "I mean, it's pretty dangerous to do that, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "pretty", "dangerous", "to", "do", "that", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "How did you think Mitt Romney did tonight?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "think", "Mitt", "Romney", "did", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I think he was wonderful tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "was", "wonderful", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What's he going to do now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "he", "going", "to", "do", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "OIGT: Well, he's going to go back and do the work that he needs to do.", "answer_tokens": ["OIGT", ":", "Well", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "go", "back", "and", "do", "the", "work", "that", "he", "needs", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "What did you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I think the fact that the most commentary following Mitt Romney's speech is about an empty chair says more about Mitt Romney than it does about Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "most", "commentary", "following", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "speech", "is", "about", "an", "empty", "chair", "says", "more", "about", "Mitt", "Romney", "than", "it", "does", "about", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "When you saw Clint Eastwood going off like he did, were you punching the air with delight?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "Clint", "Eastwood", "going", "off", "like", "he", "did", ",", "were", "you", "punching", "the", "air", "with", "delight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "No, I actually thought it was a little bit sad.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "actually", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "little", "bit", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "When you -- when you group (ph) next week and have your own convention, what are the warning signals that you have to really be alert to?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "--", "when", "you", "group", "(", "ph", ")", "next", "week", "and", "have", "your", "own", "convention", ",", "what", "are", "the", "warning", "signals", "that", "you", "have", "to", "really", "be", "alert", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Well, I think we're going to have a great convention next week.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "a", "great", "convention", "next", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Are you grouping (ph) around Hollywood, finding your own stars to speak, or is that idea gone on the back burner now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "grouping", "(", "ph", ")", "around", "Hollywood", ",", "finding", "your", "own", "stars", "to", "speak", ",", "or", "is", "that", "idea", "gone", "on", "the", "back", "burner", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "You know, our stars are the middle class and working families and the people that are powering our campaign and that will carry Barack Obama back to the White House for a second term on their shoulders.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "our", "stars", "are", "the", "middle", "class", "and", "working", "families", "and", "the", "people", "that", "are", "powering", "our", "campaign", "and", "that", "will", "carry", "Barack", "Obama", "back", "to", "the", "White", "House", "for", "a", "second", "term", "on", "their", "shoulders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Are we going to carry on seeing very, very unpleasant attack ads through his super-PAC, the very same super-PAC ads that Barack Obama vowed not get involved with?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "going", "to", "carry", "on", "seeing", "very", ",", "very", "unpleasant", "attack", "ads", "through", "his", "super-PAC", ",", "the", "very", "same", "super-PAC", "ads", "that", "Barack", "Obama", "vowed", "not", "get", "involved", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Well, Barack Obama isn't involved with super-PACs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Barack", "Obama", "is", "n't", "involved", "with", "super-PACs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Do you believe Karl Rove is still weaving his magic behind the scenes?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "Karl", "Rove", "is", "still", "weaving", "his", "magic", "behind", "the", "scenes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karl Rove"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Isn't it as simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "as", "simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, it is as simple as that but is the case of election being for sale.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "as", "simple", "as", "that", "but", "is", "the", "case", "of", "election", "being", "for", "sale", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$40 million"], "LOCATION": ["New York"], "PERSON": ["David Coke"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What about saying we're not going to try to win this by money alone?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "saying", "we", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "try", "to", "win", "this", "by", "money", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Well, that's a recipe -- you have David Coke in the New York delegation saying he will give as much as $40 million.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "recipe", "--", "you", "have", "David", "Coke", "in", "the", "New", "York", "delegation", "saying", "he", "will", "give", "as", "much", "as", "$", "40", "million", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Penn Jillette"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Even in the \"Wall Street Journal\" Rove's own colleagues are saying isn't this a complete perversion of the electoral process?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "in", "the", "``", "Wall", "Street", "Journal", "''", "Rove", "'s", "own", "colleagues", "are", "saying", "is", "n't", "this", "a", "complete", "perversion", "of", "the", "electoral", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "To Penn Jillette.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "Penn", "Jillette", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "So when the Supreme Court gave a green license to all of this, you were quite happy, were you, even though the effects surely, surely is that there will be an ever bigger corruption about the American process?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "gave", "a", "green", "license", "to", "all", "of", "this", ",", "you", "were", "quite", "happy", ",", "were", "you", ",", "even", "though", "the", "effects", "surely", ",", "surely", "is", "that", "there", "will", "be", "an", "ever", "bigger", "corruption", "about", "the", "American", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I don't know -- if you don't have, that if you don't allow people to spend money, then incumbents always win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "have", ",", "that", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "allow", "people", "to", "spend", "money", ",", "then", "incumbents", "always", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Does it get any better for a columnist in the history of journalism than Clint Eastwood going bonkers on the stage?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "get", "any", "better", "for", "a", "columnist", "in", "the", "history", "of", "journalism", "than", "Clint", "Eastwood", "going", "bonkers", "on", "the", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "In this convention, it was awesome.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "this", "convention", ",", "it", "was", "awesome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Who do you make on it?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "make", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "It will be, what the hell was Clint Eastwood's smoking?", "question_tokens": ["It", "will", "be", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "was", "Clint", "Eastwood", "'s", "smoking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "You know, there was nothing to say that it was completely da-da.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "was", "nothing", "to", "say", "that", "it", "was", "completely", "da-da", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Why are you fringing, Maeve?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "fringing", ",", "Maeve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I think also the reason it was so tense-worthy for the Romney campaign is that they are the most button downed control campaign that I have ever seen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "also", "the", "reason", "it", "was", "so", "tense-worthy", "for", "the", "Romney", "campaign", "is", "that", "they", "are", "the", "most", "button", "downed", "control", "campaign", "that", "I", "have", "ever", "seen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Maeve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "But you have Romney advisers staring open-mouthed like statues wondering, what in the hell is he going to say next?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "have", "Romney", "advisers", "staring", "open-mouthed", "like", "statues", "wondering", ",", "what", "in", "the", "hell", "is", "he", "going", "to", "say", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "He must have clear the empty chairs then.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "must", "have", "clear", "the", "empty", "chairs", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Republican Party"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What would it do to the party's reputation that they unleashed Clint Eastwood tonight and he did what he did?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "it", "do", "to", "the", "party", "'s", "reputation", "that", "they", "unleashed", "Clint", "Eastwood", "tonight", "and", "he", "did", "what", "he", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I think these things are supposed to be very carefully scripted infomercials with this very, very careful messages to frame Mitt Romney as the avatar, this young, new kind of head -- maybe not hip but certainly fresh face for the Republican Party.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "these", "things", "are", "supposed", "to", "be", "very", "carefully", "scripted", "infomercials", "with", "this", "very", ",", "very", "careful", "messages", "to", "frame", "Mitt", "Romney", "as", "the", "avatar", ",", "this", "young", ",", "new", "kind", "of", "head", "--", "maybe", "not", "hip", "but", "certainly", "fresh", "face", "for", "the", "Republican", "Party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Ryan, did Mitt Romney do enough tonight, do you think, to satisfy not just the party but the outer world?", "question_tokens": ["Ryan", ",", "did", "Mitt", "Romney", "do", "enough", "tonight", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "satisfy", "not", "just", "the", "party", "but", "the", "outer", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Mitt Romney, hit or miss?", "question_tokens": ["Mitt", "Romney", ",", "hit", "or", "miss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Clint Eastwood"], "PERSON": ["Penn Jillette"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Ben?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I think Penn Jillette is auditioning for the role of Clint Eastwood next week.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Penn", "Jillette", "is", "auditioning", "for", "the", "role", "of", "Clint", "Eastwood", "next", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Maeve?", "question_tokens": ["Maeve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I think Obama really needs to lay out his agenda for a second term and we are still waiting for that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Obama", "really", "needs", "to", "lay", "out", "his", "agenda", "for", "a", "second", "term", "and", "we", "are", "still", "waiting", "for", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}, "docId": "120830pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Joel?", "question_tokens": ["Joel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "I want - I think he can get Clint Eastwood to come to both conventions.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "-", "I", "think", "he", "can", "get", "Clint", "Eastwood", "to", "come", "to", "both", "conventions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]